LoanerLaptops program README:

Loanerlaptops.jar is what crawls the excel sheet and outputs to the log file.

LoanerLaptops.xlsx is the excel sheet tied to the Loaner Laptops Sharepoint list.

RunJava.ps1 is a powershell script that opens the excel sheet, refreshes the data so it's up to date, and runs the jar file.

LoanerLog.txt is the output/log file.

runPsScript.bat is NOT NEEDED for manually running the program.  This is used to schedule a daily task

To run on local machine:
1. Copy the folder containing the jar, excel, powershell script and log file to local machine.
2. To ensure that the data is updating properly:  
	Open the excel file > go to 'Data' (default is 'Home') > click 'Refresh All'  
	OR: Open excel file > hit 'CTRL + ALT + F5'
3. To run the program manually, simply double click the RunJava file.
4. I currently have this set up to run at 7am every day I am logged in to my laptop.  This helps me keep track of everything. 
To do that you'll need to add an event in Event Viewer and make sure that the "Run when user is logged in" is checked, otherwise
the AHS constables won't let it run.  

